wateen.net 2011-05-13

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Wateen Infotainment Portal is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Wateen Infotainment Portal Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Wateen Infotainment Portal website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from:

  * Web server cookie stored on your hard drive
  * An IP address, assigned to the computer which you use 
  * The domain server through which you access our service
  * The type of computer you're using 
  * The type of web browser you're using 

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you:

  * Name including first and last name
  * Alternate email address 
  * Mobile phone number and contact details 
  * Postal code 
  * Demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned); 
  * Preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on); 
  * Financial information (like account or credit card numbers); and 
  * Opinions of features on our websites. 

**We may also collect the following information:**

About the pages you visit/access   
The links you click on our site   
The number of times you access the page. You can terminate your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.   
Use of your Personal Information

Wateen Infotainment Portal collects and uses your personal information to operate the Wateen Infotainment Portal Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Wateen Infotainment Portal also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Wateen Infotainment Portal and its affiliates. Wateen Infotainment Portal may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

Wateen Infotainment Portal does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Wateen Infotainment Portal may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Wateen Infotainment Portal may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Wateen Infotainment Portal, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Wateen Infotainment Portal does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Wateen Infotainment Portal keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Wateen Infotainment Portal, in order to determine what Wateen Infotainment Portal services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Wateen Infotainment Portal to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

Wateen Infotainment Portal Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Wateen Infotainment Portal or the site. 
  * Protect and defend the rights or property of Wateen Infotainment Portal. 
  * Act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Wateen Infotainment Portal, or the public. 

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier and secured for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. Reference for cookies can be found at [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/)

We use session cookies to store the secure session and browsing preferences of the user. We set a persistent cookie to store your username and interests so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited. Cookies are used in shopping cart to enable enhanced security and ensuring there is no URL based spamming.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) set cookies while delivering banners on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Wateen Infotainment Portal only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

We do use cookies on point of collection pages of email address but we do not use them in emails.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Wateen Infotainment Portal secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Wateen Infotainment Portal secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Policy Updates**

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

If we decide to make changes in our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we decide to change our email practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

You are can offer your views, suggestions, if any, by submitting the filled in feedback form online.

**Contact Information**

You can contact us at:

Wateen Telecom (Pvt) Ltd.  
4th Floor, New Auriga Center  
Main Boulevard  
Gulberg II, Lahore  
PAKISTAN  
Tel: +92 42 111 999 919   
Fax: +92 42 5787001  
Email id: [portal@wateen.net](mailto:portal@wateen.net)
